With that name and your sword skills,
are you the real deal or what?
If he knows me, I should know him.
That's it!
He's an SAO survivor!
Who is he?
And where did we meet an SAO?
Answer the question, Or
don't you understand?
No, I don't.
What do you mean by real deal?
Never mind.
Whether you're a fake using
his name or the real guy,
someday I'll kill you.
I don't know what to do I don't know what
to do I don't know what to do I don't know
I'm so happy with the tears
I'm afraid of the sweetest.
How do you know?
I'm afraid of the tears.
This is the foundation.
I'm going to bring a new life.
I'll never forget it.
Thank
you so
much for watching.
The sound of the fire will
turn to the beginning.
Laughing Coffin.
God knows how many players
they killed in their time.
But they're not the only
ones guilty of murder.
If the tip we got's good, we should
be near Laughing Coffin's base.
But before we charge in,
let's keep one thing in mind.
Those guys are red players.
Once the battle starts, they're not gonna
think twice about killing any one of us.
So don't you hesitate.
You do and you're dead.
We've got two things going for us though.
We outnumber them and we've
got higher skill levels.
So who knows?
Maybe they'll surrender peacefully.
Hell, a guy.
I can dream, can't he?
Damn it!
Someone must delete our
plans, these bastards!
They caught us off guard,
but we regrouped in time.
We can do this!
You're outnumbered surrender now or else.
Come on drop your sword.
Do it you can't take another hit.
Drop the sword now.
It turned into a blood-soaked
nightmare after that.
We won the battle, but by the time
it was over, we'd lost ten of ours.
As for Laughing Coffin, twenty of them
refused to surrender and were killed.
Out of that twenty, two lives
were claimed by my sword.
That guy if he's one of the survivors from
laughing coffin then he
must have talked to me at
some point after that
battle or maybe he's one
of the two people i killed
no that's impossible?
That's crazy.
The name I share with
this weapon. Death Gun.
Oh my god.
His voice was the same as Death Gun's.
Was that him?
Could he be Death Gun?
You look like you're about to lose it.
No, I'm okay.
Guess your first match was
tougher than you thought.
You got back pretty early, though.
Not too shabby for a noob.
God, if you're like this after one match,
you'll never make it to the finals.
You better man up, guy.
Remember, we got things to settle.
Hey, let go!
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
Oh
That player got a death wish or what?
I can't believe he keeps
winning fighting like that.
His next match is in the semifinals.
Yours is, too.
So get out there and rock.
Good luck.
Stinger's my target.
His main weapon is an
FN Scar Carbine Rifle.
As a sniper, if I let him
get too close, I'm done for.
But on this map, if he
wants to close in on me,
he's going to have to go through there.
And that's where I'll take him out.
Damn him.
He wanted me to waste my first shot
to buy him time so he could advance.
Too bad for him, cause I know
the path my first bullet took.
My second one will be right on target.
You should have got out of the car, buddy.
If you did, you might have seen the
bullet lying in time to dodge it.
I don't know.
He's gonna try and close in on
me, using the shadows for cover.
My only chance is nailing him with the first
shot before he figures out my location.
He won't even know what hit him.
What's my problem?
Why do I want to beat him so bad?
Is it because he reminds me of me?
Does he think he can dodge
my bullet at this range?
Does he even want to?
Don't, don't, don't screw with me!
Uh…
Uh… Uh!
fight me come on fight or maybe
you think i'm not worth the effort
you got it all wrong all i
want is to compete in the final
there's no reason to fight
anymore then go on and shoot
yourself and get it over with or
would that be a waste of ammo or
maybe you wanted me to shoot
you because you thought it would
even the score between us to
you it's just a game just one
stupid match that's all it is
to you is that is a game well
just because you feel that way
doesn't mean i do but if we do
meet in the final bracket of
the prelims i'll be playing to
win oh i get it all right if we
both make it No holding back.
I'm sorry.
What I did was wrong.
Sure, it's a game.
It's only one match.
But still, that's why we
have to give it all we got.
It's why we're here.
It's how we live, how we keep surviving.
If anyone should have known that, it's me.
Sinon, give me a chance
to make it right with you.
Let me give you the fight I promised.
I swear, if you're messing with me...
You got any bullets left
on you, or are you out?
Yeah, I got one.
Okay, then let's have a duel.
Here's the rules.
We'll stand 10 meters apart.
You with your rifle, and me with my sword.
I'll toss this bullet up, and
when it hits the ground, we start.
What do you say?
Hang on.
If we're 10 meters away from each other,
it won't give you enough time to
see the bullet line and react.
And with my Hecate,
I'll definitely hit you.
At that range, I can't miss.
You won't know for sure till you try.
Why is he acting so confident?
Does he have a plan or something?
Whatever it is, I'm ready for it.
Okay, if that's how you want it, let's go.
I knew it.
He does have a plan.
Okay, get set.
Oh, my God.
No way!
That's impossible!
You knew where I was aiming.
But how?
How'd you know I was going for your leg?
I knew because I could see your
eye through the lens of your scope.
That's how he predicted my bullet's path?
That's amazing.
That kind of power is
way beyond any VR game.
If you're so strong you can do that,
why'd you look so afraid before?
You're wrong.
It's not strength.
All it is is a skill.
No, it's not.
Technique isn't enough to cut a
bullet from my Hecatee in half.
You and I both know that.
It takes strength, and all I
want to know is how to get it.
It's what I...
It's what I'm here to figure out.
Listen.
Could you shoot a player
in here if you knew
in the real world that
player would die from it?
And what if you had to kill that player?
Because if you didn't, you or
someone you love would die instead.
If you had that power, could
you still pull that trigger?
Does he know?
About what happened to me that day.
Or maybe something like
that happened to him too.
I can't go through that again.
So I'm not as strong as you think I am.
I don't know the names of the two.
No, three people I killed
in that other game.
I have to live with it every single day.
And every day I keep hoping I'll forget.
I'm fine.
Anyway, I guess this means I
won the duel, doesn't it? Huh?
Oh, yeah, I guess.
Well, would you mind surrendering then?
I'm not a big fan of
slashing at girls. Huh?
Next time, I'm not gonna lose.
See you in the finals.
And make sure you survive
until you see me again.
Resign!
It's my life.
More stronger, so stronger!
I want to say that I want to!
I want to be a sad feeling?
I am going to leave a whole new
past, I haven't seen any anymore.
I can't imagine a bad day
as it looks like a problem.
The pain has checked everything alone.
Thank you.
Next time, Crimson Memories.